roberttreatacademy.org 2011-10-05

# WebSchoolPro Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

At WildFireWeb, we take your privacy very seriously. We strive to ensure that your private information remains private. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the WildFireWeb web site collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web Site.   

WildFireWeb does NOT share the personal information of our customers with third parties without the specific consent of the customer.

I. Privacy   
WildFireWeb provides many different services to it's visitors, members, and customers. This policy states the company-wide Privacy Policy with regard to data collection practices. 

By visiting WildFireWeb, becoming a registered member or customer of any service, or participating in promotions, contests, etc. you hereby provide your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and are aware that our policy may change over time as discussed below. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, services and options, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of WildFireWeb Services will indicate that you agree with any changes. 

II. Nature of Information Collected   
There are two types of information collected by WildFireWeb : (A) anonymous and (B) personally identifiable information. The WildFireWeb Network's collection practices regarding these two are discussed in greater detail below. 

A. Anonymous Information Collection   
Anonymous information refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. As with visiting any web site, WildFireWeb collects some basic information about your computer, including browser type, operating system, IP address, Internet service provider and geographic location. 

B. Personally Identifiable Information   
Personally identifiable information can be used to directly identify an individual. WildFireWeb requires personal information to be collected in order to create your account. 

III. Use of Cookies   
WildFireWeb uses cookies throughout our web sites. A cookie is simply a small data file sent to your computer that identifies your computer to a specific web site. It also collects anonymous information and tracks traffic patterns. A cookie will not provide any personally identifiable information about you, nor will it read data off of your hard drive, or read cookie files created by other web sites. WildFireWeb uses the information provided by a cookie for maintaining a persistent editing session while you are logged in. 

IV. Purposes for Which Information is Collected   
WildFireWeb tracks anonymous information to determine which pages are preferred based on traffic to those areas and provide marketing information to our advertisers and sponsors. This information is aggregated to provide WildFireWeb with demographic and other statistical data that allows us to assess how well our web site is performing.

The personal information collected from our members and customers, or anyone that submits their personal information, is used to create and maintain the services requested. This includes corresponding with our members and customers by e-mail, postal mail, or phone. This correspondence is for the purpose of keeping our members and customers up to date with important system announcements and updates, and also for offering relevant third party opportunities via email. Unsubscribe procedures from non-account maintenance notifications are posted at the bottom of each email. 

V. Sharing of Information Collected byWildFireWeb   
WildFireWeb does NOT share the personal information of our customers with third parties without the specific consent of the customer. 

WildFireWeb will cooperate, as appropriate, with police, judicial and other law enforcement agencies and disclose personal information and data upon receipt of the appropriate court orders. WildFireWeb reserves the right in the absence of a court order, to release information concerning a member or customer who WildFireWeb believes is using WildFireWeb services for illegal activities. 

VI. Links to Third Parties   
WildFireWeb's web sites contain links to other web sites. When accessing the web sites of third parties, including through ad banners and other links, you will be accessing sites that are not operated or controlled by WildFireWeb . These sites may collect anonymous and personal information by various methods, including the use of cookies. The privacy policies of these web sites may not be the same as those of WildFireWeb and may not afford visitors and citizens the same level of protection. Visitors and citizens should contact these advertisers to verify the privacy policies of these web sites and their terms of use when accessing them and prior to providing any anonymous or personal information. 

VII. Storage and Security   
Data collected by WildFireWeb is stored in secure servers located in the United Sates. WildFireWeb has security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under its control. These security measures include the necessary protection to prevent, as far as possible, access to WildFireWeb databases to parties other than WildFireWeb . The utmost care is maintained to ensure your personal information is not at risk. 

VIII. Review, Correction of Information and Deactivation of Membership   
Customers and Members who have submitted personal information may, at any time, review the information relating to them contained in WildFireWeb databases and edit any incorrect information. To review the information follow the instructions provided within your account. 

A member or customer may decide at any time to terminate his/her relationship with WildFireWeb . Upon termination personal information is removed from WildFireWeb's databases. Please be advised that because of backups, and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete all information about a customer without some residual information still remaining. 

IX. Protection of Minors   
The protection of children's online privacy is very important to The WildFireWeb Network. For that reason, it is our policy not to collect or maintain information at our web sites from those we actually know are under 13 and no part of our web sites is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

At WildFireWeb, we take your privacy very seriously. We strive to ensure that your private information remains private. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the WildFireWeb web site collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web Site.   

WildFireWeb does NOT share the personal information of our customers with third parties without the specific consent of the customer.

**I. Privacy**  
WildFireWeb provides many different services to it's visitors, members, and customers. This policy states the company-wide Privacy Policy with regard to data collection practices. 

By visiting WildFireWeb, becoming a registered member or customer of any service, or participating in promotions, contests, etc. you hereby provide your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and are aware that our policy may change over time as discussed below. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, services and options, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of WildFireWeb Services will indicate that you agree with any changes. 

**II. Nature of Information Collected**  
There are two types of information collected by WildFireWeb : (A) anonymous and (B) personally identifiable information. The WildFireWeb Network's collection practices regarding these two are discussed in greater detail below.   
**  
A. Anonymous Information Collection**  
Anonymous information refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. As with visiting any web site, WildFireWeb collects some basic information about your computer, including browser type, operating system, IP address, Internet service provider and geographic location.   
**  
B. Personally Identifiable Information**  
Personally identifiable information can be used to directly identify an individual. WildFireWeb requires personal information to be collected in order to create your account. 

**III. Use of Cookies  
**

WildFireWeb uses cookies throughout our web sites. A cookie is simply a small data file sent to your computer that identifies your computer to a specific web site. It also collects anonymous information and tracks traffic patterns. A cookie will not provide any personally identifiable information about you, nor will it read data off of your hard drive, or read cookie files created by other web sites. WildFireWeb uses the information provided by a cookie for maintaining a persistent editing session while you are logged in. 

**IV. Purposes for Which Information is Collected**  
WildFireWeb tracks anonymous information to determine which pages are preferred based on traffic to those areas and provide marketing information to our advertisers and sponsors. This information is aggregated to provide WildFireWeb with demographic and other statistical data that allows us to assess how well our web site is performing.

The personal information collected from our members and customers, or anyone that submits their personal information, is used to create and maintain the services requested. This includes corresponding with our members and customers by e-mail, postal mail, or phone. This correspondence is for the purpose of keeping our members and customers up to date with important system announcements and updates, and also for offering relevant third party opportunities via email. Unsubscribe procedures from non-account maintenance notifications are posted at the bottom of each email. 

**  
V. Sharing of Information Collected byWildFireWeb**  
WildFireWeb does NOT share the personal information of our customers with third parties without the specific consent of the customer. 

WildFireWeb will cooperate, as appropriate, with police, judicial and other law enforcement agencies and disclose personal information and data upon receipt of the appropriate court orders. WildFireWeb reserves the right in the absence of a court order, to release information concerning a member or customer who WildFireWeb believes is using WildFireWeb services for illegal activities.   
**  
VI. Links to Third Parties**  
WildFireWeb's web sites contain links to other web sites. When accessing the web sites of third parties, including through ad banners and other links, you will be accessing sites that are not operated or controlled by WildFireWeb . These sites may collect anonymous and personal information by various methods, including the use of cookies. The privacy policies of these web sites may not be the same as those of WildFireWeb and may not afford visitors and citizens the same level of protection. Visitors and citizens should contact these advertisers to verify the privacy policies of these web sites and their terms of use when accessing them and prior to providing any anonymous or personal information. 

**VII. Storage and Security**  
Data collected by WildFireWeb is stored in secure servers located in the United Sates. WildFireWeb has security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under its control. These security measures include the necessary protection to prevent, as far as possible, access to WildFireWeb databases to parties other than WildFireWeb . The utmost care is maintained to ensure your personal information is not at risk. 

**VIII. Review,** Correction of Information and Deactivation of Membership   
Customers and Members who have submitted personal information may, at any time, review the information relating to them contained in WildFireWeb databases and edit any incorrect information. To review the information follow the instructions provided within your account. 

A member or customer may decide at any time to terminate his/her relationship with WildFireWeb . Upon termination personal information is removed from WildFireWeb's databases. Please be advised that because of backups, and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete all information about a customer without some residual information still remaining. 

**IX. Protection of Minors**  
The protection of children's online privacy is very important to The WildFireWeb Network. For that reason, it is our policy not to collect or maintain information at our web sites from those we actually know are under 13 and no part of our web sites is structured to attract anyone under 13.
